Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Botany Records 1882-1972
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1891-1936
  - Subseries 1: Prints
    - Indiana, AEP-INP181, A lagoon between beach ridges, Pine, Indiana AEP-INP182, A lagoon between beach ridges, Pine, Indiana AEP-INP187, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Iowa, AEP-IAP1, A ravine behind loess hills near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP2, The west slope on the east side of a gulch, Iowa AEP-IAP3, A view north of Elm and Cottonwood in the Floyd River bottom near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP4, Loess bluffs along the Floyd River with trees on the northeast exposure, Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP5, Loess bluffs along the Missouri River bottom, Iowa AEP-IAP6, Loess bluffs along the Missouri River near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP7, Bluffs along the Floyd River channel, Iowa AEP-IAP8, Loess bluffs near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP9, A loess bluff near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP10, Bluffs between Sioux City and Sargents Bluff, Iowa AEP-IAP11, A view looking east from the Missouri River bottom between Sioux City and Sargents Bluff, Iowa AEP-IAP12, The north slope of loess hills, Iowa (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Iowa, AEP-IAP13, A bluff facing west with trees on the northward point, Iowa AEP-IAP14, Bluffs with trees and grasses along the Floyd River, Iowa AEP-IAP15, A view from the bluffs into the Missouri Valley near Sioux City Iowa AEP-IAP16, A mesophytic forest in the Missouri River bottom at the base of loess hills near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP17, A view of the Missouri River bottom near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP18, Land near Burlington, Iowa AEP-IAP19, Bunch Grass on a blowhole near Burlington, Iowa AEP-IAP20, A sand blowhole, Iowa AEP-IAP21, A sand blowhole near Burlington, Iowa AEP-IAP22, Sumac foliage, Crapo Park, Iowa (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Iowa, AEP-IAP23, A cut through loess bluffs near Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP24, A twelve year old railroad cut through loess, Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP25, Swallow nests in loess bluffs, Sioux City, Iowa AEP-IAP26, A fifty year old Helianthus over ten feet high, Iowa AEP-IAP27, An ordinary upland prairie, northwestern Iowa (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Kansas, AEP-KSP1, A line of Quercus prinoides at the top of a bluff, Manhattan, Kansas AEP-KSP2, A mesophytic forest in a creek bed, Manhattan, Kansas (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP1, Bangor, Maine AEP-MEP2, Mt. Katahdin from Camp Ross, Maine AEP-MEP3, The bank of Chimney Pond, Maine showing the tree line AEP-MEP4, The bank of Chimney Pond, Maine showing the tree line AEP-MEP5, Lake Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP6, Sandy beach and dunes in a cove, Mt. Desert Island, Maine AEP-MEP7, The top of Green Mountain, Mt. Desert Island, Maine AEP-MEP8, A dry pond on Mt. Katahdin, Maine (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP9, A dry pond on Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP10, A peat bog, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP11, West bank of a peat bog, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP12, North bank of a peat bog, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP13, East bank of a peat bog, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP14, A mesophytic forest with Mt. Katahdin, Maine in the distance AEP-MEP15, Mt. Katahdin as seen from Lunksoos Mountain, Maine AEP-MEP16, Mt. Katahdin as seen from Lake Katahdin, Maine (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP17, Mt. Katahdin, Maine as seen from a sandy stream pond AEP-MEP18, Mt. Katahdin, Maine as seen from a sandy stream pond AEP-MEP19, The north basin of Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP20, The slide, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP21, View from Chimney Pond of the upper Spruce limit on Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP22, West talus slope of Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP23, Monument Peak, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP24, Green lichens common to Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP25, Section of Spruce, Mt. Katahdin, Maine (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP26, Solidago in Maine AEP-MEP27, Sedum in Maine AEP-MEP28, Salix uva-ursi in Maine AEP-MEP29, Lunksoos Mountain seen from the east branch of the Penobscot River, Maine AEP-MEP30, Wassataquoik Stream at the ford, Maine AEP-MEP31, Wassataquoik Stream joins the Penobscot River, Maine AEP-MEP32, East branch of the Penobscot River looking up at and from a ridge, Maine AEP-MEP33, Junction of the Wassataquoik Stream with the Penobscot River, Maine AEP-MEP34, The Penobscot River a mile from Lunksoos Mountain, Maine AEP-MEP35, East branch of the Penobscot River looking down the rear of a ridge, Maine (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP36, The east side of a mountain east of the Pamola summit, Maine AEP-MEP37, Rock structure of Monument Peak, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP38, West talus of the Pamola summit, Maine AEP-MEP39, Crest of the Pamola summit, Maine AEP-MEP40, East slope of the Pamola summit, Maine AEP-MEP41, Boulder on a slope of Pamola summit, Maine AEP-MEP42, Harbor at Rockland, Maine AEP-MEP43, Mosquito Mountain taken from an area near Rockland, Maine AEP-MEP44, Rocky shore on arrival from tide line near rocks, lichens gone, Rockland, Maine AEP-MEP45, Sunset beyond the mountain, Maine AEP-MEP46, Sunset from the Table Land, Maine (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP47, A Maine dry brook AEP-MEP48, A Maine dry brook near "Camp Cowles" AEP-MEP49, Brook inlet of Depot Pond with Mt. Katahdin in the background, Maine AEP-MEP50, Roaring Brook, Maine AEP-MEP51, Road from Lunksoos Mountain about a mile from the Penobscot River toward Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP52, Yellow Birch along the Penobscot River, Maine AEP-MEP53, General view into the mesophytic woods, Maine (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Maine, AEP-MEP54, Interior of mesophytic Picea forest, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP55, Picea on the trail from "Camp Cowles" to North Basin, Mt. Katahdin, Maine AEP-MEP56, Yellow Birch in Maine near "Camp Cowles" AEP-MEP57, Birch growing over a rock, Maine AEP-MEP58, Near the ford of the Penobscot River, Maine (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Maryland, AEP-MDP1, Taxodium distichum in a park high atop one small knee, Maryland AEP-MDP2, Deciduous forest with Pine one ridge in distance, Loch Haven, Maryland (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP3, A view from Mt. Pisgah looking across Forest Lake and Abies balsamea, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP4, A hydrophytic shore, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP5, A hydrophytic shore, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP6, A hydrophytic shore, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP7, Botanizing on Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP8, Wind swept sand dunes, Beaver Island, Michigan (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP9, A general view of young dunes with older partially regenerated conifer clad dunes in the background, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP10, Wind sweep which has broken through a coniferous forest on the lakeward slope, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP11, Juniperus communis in a pasture, Beaver Island, Michigan AEP-MIP12, Men from a University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class on Beaver Island, Michigan "after the girls had gone" AEP-MIP13, Dunes with Ammophila ridges west of Glen Lake, Glen Haven, Michigan AEP-MIP14, Andropogon on a morainic plain, Glen Haven, Michigan AEP-MIP15, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class at Sleeping Bear complex, Glen Haven, Michigan AEP-MIP16, The face of a landslide, an eroding shore at Sleeping Bear Point, Glen Haven, Michigan AEP-MIP17, The face of an advancing dune west of Glen Lake covering a plowed field, Glen Haven, Michigan AEP-MIP18, Days Farm with Pyramid Point in the distance as seen across a bare dune, Glen Haven, Michigan (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP19, Houghton and Hancock, Michigan AEP-MIP20, A young forest of Abies balsamea, Houghton, Michigan AEP-MIP21, Bracket fungi on a dead tree, Houghton, Michigan AEP-MIP22, Sugar Loaf Rock, an erosion remnant, Mackinac Island, Michigan AEP-MIP23, The harbor at Mackinac Island, Michigan AEP-MIP24, Near Arch Rock, Mackinac Island (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP25, Maple seedling in the interior of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP26, Andropogon mounds, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP27, Cactus at the foot of a sand dune, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP28, A view of fallen trunks of Thuja in the Cedar swamp near Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP29, Beech pool on the north shore, North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP30, Juniper heath with Red Pine, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP31, Juniper south of the lakeshore village, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP32, Shrubs at the front edge of a Larix laricina swamp, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP33, A swamp on North Manitou Island, Michigan with zones of Nymphaea, Menyanthes trifoliata, Carex, and Larix AEP-MIP34, The edge of a swamp showing zones of Sedge, Larch, and shrub, North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP35, Lycopodium, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP36, Monotropa, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP37, A Potamogeton swamp along the west shore of South Manitou, Island, Michigan AEP-MIP38, Cottonwood on sand dunes, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP39, Pteris aquilina in the interior of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP40, Rhus typhina near the life saving station at the east shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP41, Great Lakes Sand Cherries on a sand dune, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP42, Betula papyrifera with lichen on its trunk, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP43, A pasture with a thicket of Rhus and other plants north of the village, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP44, An Arborvitae swamp in the interior of North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP45, An Arborvitae swamp in the interior of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP46, In a ravine between Lake Manitou and Lake Michigan, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP47, Henry Chandler Cowles and a University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class on the shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP48, The shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP49, The shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP50, An outlet of Lake Manitou into an Arborvitae Swamp, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP51, The northeast shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP52, A raised beach on the northwest shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP53, The west shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP54, A path through the woods to Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP55, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class led by Henry Chandler Cowles, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP56, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class at lunch on the east shore of Lake Manitou, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP57, On North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP58, A fire clearing, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP59, A fire clearing on the east shore, North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP60, A beach with driftwood and forested bluffs, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP61, The interior of a mesophytic forest, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP62, The interior of a mesophytic forest northwest of the village, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP63, Shoreline of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP64, Bluffs on the northern end of North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP65, Alluvial fans on the north shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP66, Alluvial fans on the north shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP68, Bluffs on the north shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP69, The north shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP70, Sand dunes west of the point on the south end of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP71, An old beach at the south end of North Manitou Island, Michigan (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP72, Looking west along the south shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP73, Looking west from the light house on the south shore of North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP74, The east shore just north of the light house, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP75, The east shore near the light house, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP76, East shore looking north from the pier, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP77, A pier on the east shore, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP78, Larix laricina in the interior, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP79, Showing a line between the clay foundation of the island and sand, Michigan AEP-MIP80, The northwest shore of "Carp Lake" near Rotoskey, Michigan AEP-MIP81, A lifesaving station, North Manitou Island, Michigan AEP-MIP82, A dead forest of Tsuga canadensis with thick undergrowth now starting up, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP83, Gravelly shore with Pinus resinosa (red pine), Marquette, Michigan (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP84, A forest of Pinus resinosa, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP85, A typical undrained swamp (peat bog) with zones of Sedge, Larch, Spruce, and shrub, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP86, A granite island showing pioneer vegetation, herbs, krummholz, and mosses in small crevices and furrows, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP87, Granite islands, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP88, A quartzite hill forested with Pine, Mt. Mesnard, Michigan AEP-MIP89, Red Pine on granite cliffs above Lake Superior, Marquette, Michigan (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP90, A view from Mt. Mesnard of a Thuja swamp and central moraine, with granite hills in the background, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP91, The roots of Pinus resinosa exposed to severe wind action, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP92, Falls on Dead River, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP93, Dead River, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP94, Dead River, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP95, Dead River, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP96, Dead River, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP97, Dead River, Marquette, Michigan (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP98, Alnus incana in the valley of a small stream with Thuja occidentalis on the slopes, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP99, A springy hillside with Thuja occidentalis, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP100, A view of the country with terraces in the river valley, looking south and southeast from Mt. Mesnard, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP101, A general view of Sugar Loaf Peak from the shore of Lake Superior, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP102, A pond covered by Lemna, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP103, A typical undrained peat bog with zones of Sedge, Larch, and shrub, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP104, An undrained peat bog with the original lake in the foreground backed by zones of Sedge and conifer, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP105, A typical undrained peat bog with Sedge, Menyanthes trifoliata, and conifer, Marquette, Michigan (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP106, Granite hills along the shore of Lake Superior near Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP107, Granite islands in Lake Superior, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP108, A Pinus resinosa growing in a crevice, its roots causing cracking and uplifting of the granite rock, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP109, A Pinus resinosa growing in a crevice, its roots causing cracking and uplifting of the granite rock, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP110, Pinus resinosa on a granite island with lichen patches on the rocks in the foreground, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP111, Dry knolls with Cladonia rangiferina, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP112, Young clearing forest of Betula papyrifera, Marquette, Michigan (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP113, Transition forest of Red Pine, Birch, and Poplar, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP114, Forest of Pinus banksiana, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP115, Forest of Tsuga canadensis, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP116, Forest of Tsuga canadensis, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP117, Tsuga canadensis forest with an undergrowth of Lycopodium lucidulum and Taxus canadensis in the distance, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP118, Clearing with relicts of Pinus resinosa and seedling of the more xerophytic Pinus banksiana, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP119, A dead Tsuga forest with subsequent vegetation of Epilobium angustifolium, Marquette, Michigan (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Michigan, AEP-MIP120, Fungi growing on a dead log, Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP121, George Damon Fuller, professor of Plant Ecology at the University of Chicago in Newtons Woods, Michigan AEP-MIP122, Newtons Woods, Michigan AEP-MIP124, Black serpentine, Presque Isle, Michigan AEP-MIP125, Exposure of black serpentine, Presque Isle, Michigan AEP-MIP126, Lake Superior from Presque Isle, Michigan AEP-MIP127, Sandstone cliffs at Presque Isle near Marquette, Michigan AEP-MIP128, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class botanizing in Michigan (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Montana, AEP-MTP18, Echo Lake, Montana AEP-MTP19, Echo Lake, Montana AEP-MTP20, Echo Lake, Montana AEP-MTP24, Prairie swamp near Flathead Lake, Montana AEP-MTP29, Sand dunes at Mission Valley, Montana AEP-MTP31, An upland forest, Montana AEP-MTP45, A ridge formed by shore ice, Lake McDonald, Montana AEP-MTP47, A conifer forest near Swan Lake, Montana AEP-MTP48, The trunk of a Pinus Ponderosa, Bigfork, Montana AEP-MTP49, A Spruce forest near Bigfork, Montana AEP-MTP50, A Thuja forest at Belton, Montana AEP-MTP52, Three stages with Larch, Larch and Lodgepole Pine, and Lodgepole Pine, Montana (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Montana, AEP-MTP53, The reforestation of a conifer forest, Montana AEP-MTP60, The reforestation of a conifer forest, Montana AEP-MTP62, The mountains above Lake McDonald, Montana AEP-MTP63, Lake McDonald, Montana AEP-MTP65, A general view of mountains and conifer forests from Post Creek, Montana AEP-MTP67, A general view of distant mountains, Montana AEP-MTP68, A general view of distant mountains with conifer forests and treeless peaks, Montana AEP-MTP69, Mission Mountains from the top of Mt. Teton, Montana AEP-MTP70, A general view of mountains, Montana AEP-MTP71, A general view of distant mountains with conifer forests, Montana AEP-MTP74, A treeless east slope and a forested west slope on a high ridge in the Rocky Mountains, Montana (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Montana, AEP-MTP76, McDougal Peak, Montana showing the relation of vegetation to cliffs and to talus slopes AEP-MTP77, McDougal Peak, Montana showing the relation of vegetation to cliffs and to talus slopes AEP-MTP81, A general view near the tree line in the Rocky Mountains, Montana AEP-MTP82, A general view near the tree line in the Rocky Mountains, Montana AEP-MTP83, A general view near the tree line in the Rocky Mountains, Montana AEP-MTP84, A general view near the tree line in the Rocky Mountains, Montana AEP-MTP89, Alpine lakes and parks, McDougal Peak, Montana AEP-MTP92, Above the trees, Avalanche Basin, Montana AEP-MTP98, An alpine meadow in spring, Montana AEP-MTP99, The laboratory staff of the State Biological Station, Flathead Lake, Montana (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Montana, AEP-MTP100, A member of a University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class in Montana AEP-MTP101, Larch and Lodgepole, Pine, Belton, Montana AEP-MTP102, An alpine meadow in early spring in the Rocky Mountains near Flathead Lake, Montana AEP-MTP103, Xerophyllum tenax in the Rocky Mountains near Flathead Lake, Montana AEP-MTP104, The reforestation of a conifer forest, Montana AEP-MTP105, Thick forest growth, Montana AEP-MTP106, Forests along a river bank, Montana AEP-MTP107, Forested cliffs of a river canyon, Montana (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Nevada, AEP-NVP1, Opuntia parryi at the west end of Indian Spring Valley, Nevada (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - New Mexico, AEP-NMP1, Pine on hill, irrigation in foreground, Santa Fe, New Mexico AEP-NMP2, Looking southwest, Laguna, New Mexico AEP-NMP3, Near Santa Fe, New Mexico (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - New York, AEP-NYP1, "The Spit," a sand beach at Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP2, Uprooted tree in a swamp, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP3, Open Robinia pseudoacacia in New York AEP-NYP4, Robinia pseudoacacia, New York AEP-NYP5, Two kinds of leaves from Broussonetia papyrifera, New York AEP-NYP6, Fungus, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP7, Lactuca canadensis, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP8, A forest, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP9, Mesophytic forest, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP10, At Cold Spring Harbor, New York (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - New York, AEP-NYP11, An avenue of Locusts, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP12, Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP13, Yard of the Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP14, Yard of the Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP15, Dam near Carnegie Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP16, General low tide, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP17, High tide, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP18, Low tide, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP19, Pinus rigida, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP20, Quercus stellata in New York AEP-NYP21, Sassafras albidum in New York (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - New York, AEP-NYP22, Juniperus virginiana in New York AEP-NYP23, Undergrowth in a Chestnut forest, Cold Spring Harbor, New York AEP-NYP24, Castanea dentata in New York AEP-NYP25, Cornus florida in New York AEP-NYP26, Gleditsia triacanthos in New York AEP-NYP27, Liriodendron tulipifera in New York AEP-NYP28, Ailanthus altissima on the path near a railway station, New York AEP-NYP29, Robinia pseudoacacia in New York AEP-NYP30, Lighthouse and sand dunes, Fire Island, New York (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - New York, AEP-NYP31, Lighthouse and sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP32, Stratification, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP33, Ammophila breviligulata and Hudsonia tomentosa on dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP34, Sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP35, Sand dune crater, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP36, Sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP37, Sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP38, Sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP39, Sand dunes, Fire Island, New York AEP-NYP40, Juniperus virginiana branches, New York (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - New York, AEP-NYP41, Mesophytic forest, New York AEP-NYP42, Juniperus virginiana, Lloyd Neck, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP43, Salt meadow, Lloyd Neck, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP44, Salt meadow, Lloyd Neck, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP45, View from the middle of the Salicornia zone, Lloyd Neck, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP46, Beach, Lloyd Point, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP47, Robinia pseudoacacia and Ailanthus altissima, New York AEP-NYP48, General view of a dying salt marsh, Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP49, General view of a dying salt marsh, Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP50, General view of a dying salt marsh near Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - New York, AEP-NYP51, Transition from beach to Pine forest near Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP52, Erosion of moraine headland near Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP53, Juniperus virginiana near Oyster Bay, Long Island, New York AEP-NYP54, Lathyrus japonicus var. maritimus in New York AEP-NYP55, Arenaria in New York AEP-NYP56, Hudsonia tomentosa in New York AEP-NYP57, Juniperus virginiana in a pasture, New York AEP-NYP58, Hibiscus moscheutos in New York AEP-NYP59, A gneiss boulder in New York AEP-NYP60, A gneiss boulder in New York AEP-NYP61, Arctium lappa in New York (Box 46, Folder 2)